- I just got here, and I think I'm loosing signal already.
- 我刚到这里，我想 我已经失去信号了。
Hello? Can you hear me now?
你好？ 你能听到我吗？
(wind buffeting)
（风抖动）
Sorry, sorry, I'll call you later.
对不起，对不起，我稍后再打给你。
Yeah, yeah, sorry.
是的，是的，对不起。
(wind buffeting) (phone clacking)
（风吹） （电话响）
(lock clicking) (door creaking)
（锁扣） （门吱吱作响）
(footsteps echoing)
（脚步声回荡）（布料沙沙
(fabric rustling)
作响）
(Adele inhaling) (soft piano music)
（阿黛尔吸气） （轻柔的钢琴音乐）
♪ Hello, it's me ♪
♪你好，是我
♪ I was wondering if after all these years ♪
♪♪我想知道 这么多年过去了
♪ You'd like to meet ♪
♪♪ 你想见见 ♪
♪ To go over everything ♪
♪ 回顾一切 ♪
♪ They say that time's supposed to heal ya ♪
♪ 他们说时间 应该可以治愈你 ♪ ♪
♪ But I ain't done much healing ♪
但我没有做太多治疗 ♪ ♪
♪ Hello, can you hear me ♪
你好，你能听到我的声音 ♪
♪ I'm in California dreaming about who we used to be ♪
♪ 我在加利福尼亚梦见 谁 我们曾经是 ♪
♪ When we were younger and free ♪
♪ 当我们年轻而自由的时候 ♪
♪ I've forgotten how it felt ♪
♪ 我已经忘记了当时的感觉 ♪
♪ Before the world fell at our feet ♪
♪ 在世界跌倒在我们脚下之前 ♪
♪ There's such a difference between us ♪
♪ 我们之间有如此大的差异 ♪
♪ And a million miles ♪
♪ 还有一百万英里 ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ 来自对方的问候 边 ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ 我一定打了一千次电话 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for everything that I've done ♪
♪ 告诉你我为 我所做的一切感到抱歉 ♪ ♪
♪ But when I call, you never seem to be home ♪
但是当我打电话时，你 似乎永远不在家 ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ 从外面打招呼 ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ 至少 我可以说我已经试过了 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for breaking your heart ♪
♪ 告诉你我很抱歉 让你伤心 ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ 但没关系 ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ 显然它不会再把 你撕裂了 ♪
♪ Hello, how are you ♪
♪ 你好，你好吗 ♪
♪ It's so typical of me to talk about myself, I'm sorry ♪
♪ 这是 如此典型的我来 谈论 我自己，我很抱歉 ♪
♪ I hope that you're well ♪
♪ 我希望你一切都好 ♪ ♪
♪ Did you ever make it out of that town ♪
你有没有从那个小镇逃出来 ♪ ♪
♪ Where nothing ever happened ♪
那里什么都没有发生 ♪
♪ It's no secret that the both of us ♪
♪ 我们俩都不是秘密 ♪ ♪
♪ Are running out of time ♪
时间不多了 ♪
♪ So hello from the other side ♪
♪ 所以从另一边打招呼 ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ 另一边 ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ 我一定打了一千次 ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ 千次 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for everything that I've done ♪
♪ 告诉你我为 我所做的一切感到抱歉 ♪
♪ But when I call, you never seem to be home ♪
♪ 但当我打电话时，你 永远不会 似乎在家 ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
♪ 从外面打招呼 ♪ ♪ 在
♪ Outside ♪
外面 ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ 至少我可以说我试过了 ♪ ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
我试过了 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for breaking your heart ♪
♪ 告诉你我很抱歉 伤了你的心 ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
♪ 但事实并非如此 没关系 ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ 它显然不会 再把你撕裂了 ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ 高潮，高潮，高潮，高潮 ♪ ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪ ♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
哦，不再 ♪ ♪ 低谷，低谷，低谷，低谷 ♪
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
♪ 高潮，高潮，高潮，高潮 ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪ ♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ 哦，不再 ♪ ♪ 低点，低点，低点，低点 ♪ ♪ 高点，高点，高点，
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
高点 ♪
♪ Ooh, anymore ♪ ♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ 哦，再也没有了 ♪ ♪ 低点，低点，低点，低点 ♪ 高点，高点，高点
♪ Highs, highs, highs, highs ♪
，高点 ♪
♪ Anymore ♪ ♪ Lows, lows, lows, lows ♪
♪ 再也没有了 ♪ ♪ 低点，低点， 低点，低点 ♪
♪ Hello from the other side ♪
♪ 从另一边打招呼 ♪
♪ Other side ♪
♪ 另一边 ♪
♪ I must've called a thousand times ♪
♪ 我一定打过一千次电话 ♪
♪ Thousand times ♪
♪ 千吨 时间 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for everything that I've done ♪
♪ 告诉你我为 我所做的一切感到抱歉 ♪
♪ But when I call, you never seem to be home ♪
♪ 但是当我打电话时，你 似乎永远不在家 ♪ ♪
♪ Hello from the outside ♪
从外面你好 ♪
♪ Outside ♪
♪ 在外面 ♪
♪ At least I can say that I've tried ♪
♪ 至少我可以说我已经 试过了 ♪
♪ I've tried ♪
♪ 我已经试过了 ♪
♪ To tell you I'm sorry for breaking your heart ♪
♪ 告诉你我很抱歉 让你伤心 ♪ ♪
♪ But it don't matter ♪
但没关系 ♪
♪ It clearly doesn't tear you apart anymore ♪
♪ 它显然不会再把 你撕裂了 ♪
(somber music)
（忧郁的音乐）